freedocast.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy - Freedocast

Freedocast is YuppTV group company & governed by YuppTV Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how YuppTV USA Inc. and its affiliated companies within the YuppTV Group ("YuppTV", "we", "our" or "us") collect, use, disclose, process, store, transfer and protect any personal information that you give us when you use our services. This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs the use of Personal Information shared (as defined below) with or collected from the subscriber (“you”) of YuppTV but excludes from its purview services that state that they are offered under a different privacy policy.

You acknowledge that your continued use of our YuppTV platform after we publish or send a notice about our changes to our Privacy Policy means that the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to the updated Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy describes the usage of information provided or collected on the platform and applications where this Privacy Policy is posted. We follow this Privacy Policy in accordance with applicable law in the places where we operate. In some cases, we may provide additional data privacy notices specific to certain services or regions. Those terms are to be read in combination with this policy.

Please keep in mind that when you provide information to us via third-party sites or platforms (for example, registration or sign up using social media login the information we collect is through those third-party sites linked with our applications and is covered by this Privacy Policy, however the information third-party sites or platform collects is subject to the third-party site or platform’s privacy practices. Privacy choices you have made on the third-party sites or platforms will not apply to our use of the information we have collected directly through our platform. Please also keep in observance that our platform and applications may contain links to other platforms not owned or controlled by us and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those platform. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our platform or applications; read the privacy policies of other platform that may collect your personal information.

By using our services, you consent us to collect, use, and storage of your information (including such subscriber information provided to YuppTV, from third parties, in the course of migration subject to your approval) in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies only to personal information YuppTV and its group affiliates collect about the subscriber and does not apply to personal information about the subscriber collected by any other third party website and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from YuppTV website or its services. The information collected or received by third party website are subject to their own privacy policies. 

This Privacy Policy details important information regarding the use and disclosure of subscriber information collected on the YuppTV platform to enable the subscriber to make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using the YuppTV platform and services. It is clarified that any video, image, or other subscriber content posted at the direction of the subscriber onto the YuppTV platform becomes published content and shall not be considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

“Personal Information” or “PII” is defined as any information that identifies (whether directly or indirectly) to a particular individual or natural person, such as the individual’s name, postal address, email address, and mobile number indicating to that particular person or is identifiable. When anonymous information is directly or indirectly associated with personal information, the resulting information also is treated as personal information.

We ask for and collect the following personal information about you when you use YuppTV service or platform. Without this information we may not be able to provide you with all the requested services;

  * First/Last Name
  * Mobile No.
  * Email id
  * Country
  * State
  * Role
  * Industry
  * Billing address
  * Shipping address

We collect information about you and your use of our service, your interactions with us, as well as information about your device used to access our service .The information includes;

  * Activities such as type of content, watch history, search queries etc.
  * Your interactions with our email, customer care and messaging platform.
  * Geo-location information like IP addresses.
  * Device information like device id, device model etc. and other unique identifier.s
  * Cookies are captured from your browser while you are on our platform.

If you choose to post messages on social media accounts, message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on YuppTV, we may collect and store such information. But we would notify you prior to any further processing of that information

An agent or affiliate of YuppTV may, at times and on being so authorized, collect information on behalf of YuppTV. Third party providers featured on or linked to by the YuppTV sites, such as vendors of products and services offered through the sites, may be gathering the same kind of information. 

Any personal information or video content that the user voluntarily discloses online (on discussion boards, in messages and chat areas, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. The Users account name (not the email address) is displayed to other users when any videos are uploaded or messages are sent through the services and other users can contact the user through messages and comments. Any videos that the user submits to the YuppTV sites may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public. 

Based on your purchase of a subscription package, our payment gateway partners collect information with respect to your credit/debit card details or other bank account details. This information is stored by our payment gateway partners. For instance, YuppTV will be using third party payment gateway providers to process and facilitate the payment of your subscription fee to YuppTV for providing you access to the subscription. Please note that YuppTV does not directly collect any financial information such as credit card or debit card or net banking details from you. Such payment gateway partners are not controlled by us. When you visit such payment gateways you do so at your own risk. These payment gateways may have their own privacy policies in place, which we recommend you review if you visit any such payment gateways. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for such payment gateways, the content of such payment gateways and their privacy practices, nor do we endorse them. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by such payment gateways prior to providing them with information about you or entering into any transactions with them. 

While transacting with these payment gateways, you may provide your financial information including without limitation your bank account details, credit card account details or your details pertaining to any payment settlement or pre-paid instrument service provider. You understand, agree and acknowledge that YuppTV never receives your financial and payment information from these payment gateways. Your Personal Information, Sensitive Personal Data or Information and financial information will be dealt with by these payment gateways in accordance with their respective privacy policies and other terms and conditions and YuppTV shall not be liable, accountable or responsible for Your Personal Information, Sensitive Personal Data or Information and financial information which you provide to these payment gateways. 

Except as provided herein, we do not solicit any Sensitive Information about You. However, if you share such information with us voluntarily, we will not be liable for any actions, claims, costs, expenses or other liabilities that may arise as a consequence of such any unauthorized use or misuse of such information.

  * Process and respond to your queries
  * Understand our subscriber (what they do on our services, what features they like, how they use them, etc.), improve the content and features of our services (such as by personalizing content to your interests), process and make special offers 
  * Send you communications that you have requested or that may be of interest to you by way of emails, or telephone calls, or any other mode of communication.
  * Send you contents that you may be like based on your previous viewing content if you have registered with our services.
  * Provide you with customer support.
  * Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * Notify you about changes to our services.
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features offered through our services.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-party services that may be of interest to you. If you want us to use your information in this way, please provide explicit consent for the same when we collect your data and/or adjust your subscriber preferences in your account profile w.r.t. your choices/preferences provided. We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to provide you with more relevant services and advertising purposes.

We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have lawful bases. Lawful bases include consent Where we process data based on consent, we will ask for your explicit consent (where you have given consent), and “legitimate interests” where processing is necessary by us to provide you with customer support or process your data for providing premium services (For e.g. processing your information by our payment gateway service providers).Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you may withdraw your consent at any time and where we rely on legitimate interests, you have may object to the processing.

You may withdraw your consent for the collection, use and/or disclosure of your personal information in our possession or control by submitting a request on our support e-mail or using the chat functionality or by directly contacting our support team (see contact us section). We will process your request within a reasonable time from when the request was made, and thereafter not process your personal information as per your request.

We may partner with third-party service providers to serve ads regarding goods or services that may be of interest to you when you access and use the Site and third party-platform. Some of the ads on this Site or on third party platform may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on what we or the online advertising network serving the ad know about you or your computer’s browsing activity on both the Site and third-party platform. To do so, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through the use of pixel tags).

The Network Advertising Initiative offers useful information about internet advertising companies, including information about how to opt-out of interest-based advertising by their members. See [http://www.networkadvertising.org   ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) for general information about the NAI and [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) for the opt-out page. You may also visit [http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/ ](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers/) to learn about interest-based advertising and how to opt-out from ads served by some or all participating companies. 

These opt-out mechanisms rely on cookies to remember your choices. If you delete your cookies, use another computer or device, or change browsers, you will need to repeat this process. In addition, opting out of interest-based ads will not opt you out of all ads, but rather only those ads that are personalized to your interests.

YuppTV uses IP address information for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. This information is also used to deliver web pages to the subscriber upon request; to tailor the site to the interests of the subscriber and to measure traffic within the YuppTV site.

Any personally identifiable information provided by the subscriber is used to operate, maintain, and provide the Subscriber with the features and functionality of the YuppTV platform. 

YuppTV does not use the subscriber email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without the subscriber consent. YuppTV may not use both personally identifiable information and certain non-personally- identifiable information to improve the quality and design of the services and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing subscriber preferences and trends without the subscriber consent.

YuppTV uses cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: remember information so that the subscriber is not required to re-enter it during subsequent visits; provide custom and personalized content and information; monitor the effectiveness of marketing campaigns; monitor logs such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and to track entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests of the subscriber. For more details you can go and check more information on cookies on  cookie policy.

We do not share your personal information with Companies, organizations, or individuals outside of YuppTV except in the following cases:

We’ll share or disclose your personal information outside of YuppTV when we have your consent. For example, providing SMS and E-mail related services such as marketing newsletters, promotions and offers.

We provide personal information to our affiliates and other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. For example, we disclose your personal information with the customer support team to help resolve your queries

We shall endeavour that the third parties and agents engaged by us to whom we may provide access to Your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Data or Information for the purposes set out herein are under an contractual obligation to protect Your Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Data or Information in accordance with the same standard that YuppTV has agreed to be subject to in this Privacy Policy.

In the event of any requirement by court order, government or quasi-government agency to disclose Your Personal Information, We will disclose information as may be legally required. We may also disclose Your Personal Information if we, in the good faith believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.

In the event YuppTV is merged with or acquired by another company or in case of re-organization or re-structuring of business, we and our affiliates will share Your Personal Information, wholly or in part, with another business entity. We will notify you via e-mail or update our privacy terms if any of the above merger/acquisition/restructuring does take place

We may share non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners — like publishers, advertisers, developers, or rights holders. For example, we share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services. We also allow specific partners to collect information from your browser or device for advertising and measurement purposes using their own cookies or similar technologies.

We provide you the ability to exercise certain controls and choices regarding our collection, use and sharing of your information. In accordance with applicable law, your controls and choices may include:

  * Correcting, updating, and deleting your registration account 
  * Choosing or changing your choices for subscriptions, newsletters, and alerts
  * Choosing whether to receive from us offers and promotions for our products and services, or products and services that we think may be of interest to you
  * Choosing whether we share your personal information with other companies so they can send you offers and promotions about their products and services
  * Controlling targeted advertising from many ad networks and partners; data exchanges; and marketing analytics and digital advertising and marketing service providers 
  * Choosing to control targeted advertising you receive within applications by using the settings and choices made available to you through your device(s), for example, by re-setting your device’s advertising identifier and/or opting out of interest based ads
  * Requesting removal of your personal information from our platform or application
  * Requesting access to the personal information we hold about you and that we amend or delete it.
  * Requesting a copy of the personal information we hold about you subject to restrictions on the personal information that we may be able to provide you

Please be aware that if you do not allow us to collect personal information from you, we may not be able to deliver certain experiences, products, and services to you, and some of our services may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If collection of personal information is mandatory, we will make that clear at the point of collection so that you can make an informed decision whether to participate. If you have questions about the specific personal information about you that we process or retain, and your rights regarding that personal information, please contact our customer support team.

YuppTV are not intentionally designed for or directed at persons less than 18 years of age. YuppTV does not knowingly permit any person who is under 18 years of age to register with the services or to provide any other personally identifying information. If YuppTV becomes aware that any personally identifiable information of persons less than 18 years of age has been collected on the YuppTV platform without verified parental consent, then YuppTV will take the appropriate steps to delete any such information. However, we consider it the responsibility of parents to monitor their children’s use of our services. Nevertheless, it is our policy not to require personal information from children’s below 18 years or offer to send any promotional materials to persons in that category. YuppTV does not seek or intend to seek or to receive any personal information from children’s. Should a parent or guardian have reasons to believe that a minor has provided YuppTV with personal information without their prior consent, please contact our customer support team to ensure that the personal information is removed from YuppTV. 

We operate globally and may transfer your personal information to individual companies of YuppTV or third parties in locations around the world for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and which The countries may have data protection laws that differ from those of your country Wherever your personal information is transferred, stored or processed by us, we will take reasonable steps to safeguard the privacy of your personal information. Additionally, when using or disclosing personal information transferred from the European Union, we use standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission, adopt other means under European Union law for ensuring adequate safeguards. 

Any information provided by the subscriber to YuppTV shall be stored and held under generally accepted standards of technology and operational security in order to protect the subscriber personally identifiable information from loss, misuse, alteration, or destruction. Only authorized personnel are permitted access to the subscriber information and these personnel are required to treat this information as confidential. Despite these precautions, YuppTV cannot guarantee that any and all unauthorized access to the subscriber information will be prevented. 

We retain Personal Information or Sensitive Personal Data or Information for as long as we may require unless you send a request to delete your account with us. This includes data you or others provided to us and data generated or inferred from your use of our services.

We are continuously implementing and updating administrative, technical, and physical security measures to help protect your information against unauthorized access, loss, destruction, or alteration. Some of the safeguards we use to protect your information are firewalls and data encryption, and information access controls. If you know or have reason to believe that your YuppTV account credentials have been lost, stolen, altered, or otherwise compromised or in case of any actual or suspected unauthorized use of your account, please contact us by contacting our customer support team.

Please be aware that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. By continuing to access the YuppTV platform you are aware of such risk.

YuppTV may update or revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. Please take a look at the “Effective Date” legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy. YuppTV will also notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy. Your use of the YuppTV platform following any changes to this Privacy Policy means you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

In the event that YuppTV is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, YuppTV reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the Information collected from the Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the event of bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, YuppTV may not be able to control how the Users Personal Information is treated, transferred, or used.

YuppTV shall timely address and attempt to rectify any discrepancies and grievances of our users pertaining to the personal information furnished by them. 

  * Subscriber may contact YuppTV with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy using the contact form or may address such queries and / or comments to [info@freedocast.com](mailto:info@freedocast.com)
  * If you have any queries or complaints regarding the collecting, processing, transfer of personal data/information or regarding this policy please do contact us first through [support@freedocast.com](mailto:support@freedocast.com) online. You can also reach us by physical mail. 

Freedocast,   
YuppTV India Pvt Ltd,  
8-2-293/82/A/773, Road No.44, Jubilee Hills,  
Hyderabad-500033, India. 

  * Residents in the countries in the European Union (EU), may contact our Data Protection Officer [support@freedocast.com](mailto:support@freedocast.com)
  * Residents in India may contact our Grievance Officer at suppport@freedocast.com. The Grievance Officer shall redress the grievances of the users furnishing the Information within one (1) month from the date of receipt of the grievance.
